<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> <rss version="2.0"> <channel> <title>NodeMixaholic Oeaps</title> 
<link>https://nodemixaholic.com</link> <description>Birds go tweet, elephants go toot, I go oeap. (What I think av_mouse_howl from Toontown Online Sounds Like)</description> <language>en-us</language>     <item>
        <title>Hello, World!</title>
        <author>nodemixaholic@nodemixaholic.com</author>
        <description>Hello world!

This is my first oeap, to describe what this RSS feed is about.

What is an oeap? An oeap, simply, is a descriptive term for the Toontown sound for the mouse "howling".


But... what is an oeap in this context? Simply put, it's my thoughts in their purest form. Like birds go tweet, and mastodons go toot, I oeap.


What is this RSS feed? Simply put it will be filled with Oeaps, because I wish to be more independent on the net and not rely on Twitter or Mastodon.

Hope yall enjoy your day.

Peace!</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 11:34:47 -0600</pubDate>
    </item>    <item>
        <title>Quick update regarding computing</title>
        <author>nodemixaholic@nodemixaholic.com</author>
        <description>Hello world!

As you may know, I use LINUX. My journey has been great so far. And as such
I think it's time to take it to the next step. That's right, I'm going
to be using mostly FOSS. This means NO Steam, Discord, or other not needed
distractions that are big tech. That being said, I will give a *few*
exceptions, such as using Discord exclusively for moderation of my servers.
That being said, I will use Matrix for the actual chatting, as well as
Windows virtual machines for any Windows-based development I need to do.

In addition, I will support small up-coming tech companies that support
Linux, such as Polytoria and others. I will also still be in the FOSS
community. However, don't expect me to be active on things like Discord and
Steam. Also I might not be that active on things like ROBLOX due to it's bloat
and proprietary naturre.

As always, you can email me at the email address specified.
(nodemixaholic@nodemixaholic.com)

Or if you are good friends with me, you can contact me on my Discord server
and I will reply via Matrix. :-)

Have fun out there yall, and I hope we get in touch soon.

--NM</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 10:09:15 -0600</pubDate>
    </item>    <item>
        <title>Windows sucks.</title>
        <author>nodemixaholic@nodemixaholic.com</author>
        <description>Windows sucks because:
1. it's proprietary
2. it spies on it's users
3. very little customization compared to GNU/Linux
4. insecure af</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 21:14:02 -0600</pubDate>
    </item>    <item>
        <title>RSS - A better social platform</title>
        <author>nodemixaholic@nodemixaholic.com</author>
        <description>Here are my opinions on why RSS is just the better social platform

1. only follow people who you wish

* This explains itself


2. keep informed, choose your bloat

* As in: You can keep informed about local/global stuff going on

* But with as much software bloat as you choose.


3. as much toxicity as you choose

* As in: Toxicity you see all depends on what people you follow on RSS.

* And for targeted toxicity, they would have to "follow your RSS feed" in some way</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 22:18:35 -0600</pubDate>
    </item></channel>                    
</rss>
